[{"answer": "You'd lose the mone", "docId": "Hellraiser-3-Hell-on-Earth.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "That is the story of my life", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "U", "docId": "Hellraiser-3-Hell-on-Earth.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "my friend.  Yeah, who is this", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "... well, I've been having it for years. It's not a nightmare or anything.  It's ... well, I know what it is", "docId": "Hellraiser-3-Hell-on-Earth.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Why are you so interested", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Hellraiser-3-Hell-on-Earth.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I know what you're saying but ... Never? You've never had a dream?  No, you know, you do.  You must.  What you mean is you don't remember them", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Did you know him", "docId": "Hellraiser-3-Hell-on-Earth.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Taken what", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Thank you for the drink.  And the rose. Wow.  That's ... really nice", "docId": "Hellraiser-3-Hell-on-Earth.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "A prize?  For what", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yes really", "docId": "Hellraiser-3-Hell-on-Earth.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "No.  Thank you", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You shit.  Who do you think you are", "docId": "Hellraiser-3-Hell-on-Earth.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You ... I can't fucking believe you, you bastard!  You get me in here ..", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Yeah ... yeah, it looks different", "docId": "Hellraiser-3-Hell-on-Earth.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "A girl?  Anyone I should know", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "That's terrible.  What a bitch.  She was obviously just using you, my friend.  Ready to dump you the second she had what she needed, interfering little whore", "docId": "Hellraiser-3-Hell-on-Earth.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Hey, you didn't fuck it up with me.  You know that.  It was my fault, babe, it really was.  And you know I'm sorry. And I'm sorry to see you upset now.  I hate to see you in pain like this", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well done.  Brave girl.  You've probably never shaken hands with a ghost before, am I right", "docId": "Hellraiser-3-Hell-on-Earth.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Hell is precisely what is going on, my friend.  And we have to stop it.  I because of a special obligation, you because you're the only person who can help. And because you know what is right, and just, and true.  Will you walk with me a while", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Because", "docId": "Hellraiser-3-Hell-on-Earth.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "He'll do what he does best.  But he'll do it unfettered.  He wants to walk the Earth forever, indulging his taste for all the myriad subtleties of human suffering", "qsentId": 24}]